let FquestionArr=[
    {
        question:'What is 80/2+5+5?',
        answer:50,
        color:'RV',
        number:50,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 30*2-10+1?',
        answer:51,
        color:'Green',
        number:51,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 10*5+5-3?',
        answer:52,
        color:'Red',
        number:52,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 9*7-5*2?',
        answer:53,
        color:'Green',
        number:53,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 3*20+4-10?',
        answer:54,
        color:'Red',
        number:'54',
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 80/2+13+2?',
        answer:55,
        color:'GV',
        number:55,
        size:'Big'
    },
    
    {
        question:'What is 30+20/10+24?',
        answer:56,
        color:'Red',
        number:56,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 6*9+6-3?',
        answer:57,
        color:'Green',
        number:'57',
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 2*10*2+18?',
        answer:58,
        color:'Red',
        number:58,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 25*2+5+4?',
        answer:59,
        color:'Green',
        number:59,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 16*3+6+6?',
        answer:60,
        color:'RV',
        number:60,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 20*4-20+1?',
        answer:61,
        color:'Green',
        number:61,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 70-6*2+4?',
        answer:62,
        color:'Red',
        number:62,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 5*5*3-12?',
        answer:63,
        color:'Green',
        number:63,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 14*4+20-12?',
        answer:64,
        color:'Red',
        number:64,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 100/2+40-25?',
        answer:65,
        color:'GV',
        number:65,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 100/2+40-24?',
        answer:66,
        color:'Red',
        number:66,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 40+20+2+5?',
        answer:67,
        color:'Green',
        number:67,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 30*2+4+4?',
        answer:68,
        color:'Red',
        number:68,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 70-10+3*3?',
        answer:69,
        color:'Green',
        number:69,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 25*3-15+10?',
        answer:70,
        color:'RV',
        number:70,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 25*3-15+11?',
        answer:71,
        color:'Green',
        number:71,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 80*2-90+2?',
        answer:72,
        color:'Red',
        number:72,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 38*2-2-1?',
        answer:73,
        color:'Green',
        number:73,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 40/2+60-6?',
        answer:74,
        color:'Red',
        number:74,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 15*4+10+5?',
        answer:75,
        color:'GV',
        number:75,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 19*6-14-24?',
        answer:76,
        color:'Red',
        number:76,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 9*8+2+3?',
        answer:77,
        color:'Green',
        number:77,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 4*20/2+38?',
        answer:78,
        color:'Red',
        number:78,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 17*5-10+4?',
        answer:79,
        color:'Green',
        number:79,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 200/4+20+10?',
        answer:80,
        color:'RV',
        number:80,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 12*8+4-19?',
        answer:81,
        color:'Green',
        number:81,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 350/5+30-18?',
        answer:82,
        color:'Red',
        number:82,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 35*3-35+13?',
        answer:83,
        color:'Green',
        number:83,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 10*8+2+2?',
        answer:84,
        color:'Red',
        number:84,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 15*4+35-10?',
        answer:85,
        color:'GV',
        number:85,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 50+20+10+6?',
        answer:86,
        color:'Red',
        number:86,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 50+20+10+7?',
        answer:87,
        color:'Green',
        number:87,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 99-15+2+2?',
        answer:88,
        color:'Red',
        number:88,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 9*9+16-8?',
        answer:89,
        color:'Green',
        number:89,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 10*10-5-5?',
        answer:90,
        color:'RV',
        number:90,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 30*9-200+21?',
        answer:91,
        color:'Green',
        number:91,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 30*9-200+22?',
        answer:92,
        color:'Red',
        number:92,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 13*8/4+67?',
        answer:93,
        color:'Green',
        number:93,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 63+7+8+16?',
        answer:94,
        color:'Red',
        number:94,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 21*5+5-15?',
        answer:95,
        color:'GV',
        number:95,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 55*2/10+85?',
        answer:96,
        color:'Red',
        number:96,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 6*6*3-11?',
        answer:97,
        color:'Green',
        number:97,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 6*6*3-10?',
        answer:98,
        color:'Red',
        number:98,
        size:'Big'
    },
    {
        question:'What is 18*4+30-3?',
        answer:99,
        color:'Green',
        number:99,
        size:'Big'
    },
]

const colorGame = [
    {
        question: 'What is 96/8+2-14?',
        answer: 0,
        color: 'RV',
        number: 0,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 99/11*2-17?',
        answer: 1,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 1,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 20/2*2-18?',
        answer: 2,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 2,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 99/33*12/12?',
        answer: 3,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 3,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 8*9/12-2?',
        answer: 4,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 4,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 5*50/25-1-4?',
        answer: 5,
        color: 'GV',
        number: 5,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 96/12*2-10?',
        answer: 6,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 6,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 70-50/10-58?',
        answer: 7,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 7,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 125/5*2-48+6?',
        answer: 8,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 8,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 360/20/6+6?',
        answer: 9,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 9,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 10*60/6-80-10?',
        answer: 10,
        color: 'RV',
        number: 10,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 5+6-99/11+9?',
        answer: 11,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 11,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 50-60+50/10+17?',
        answer: 12,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 12,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 138/6-20+10?',
        answer: 13,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 13,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 2*6/3+20-10?',
        answer: 14,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 14,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 125/5-25+15?',
        answer: 15,
        color: 'GV',
        number: 15,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 148/2-58?',
        answer: 16,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 16,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 58-69/3-18?',
        answer: 17,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 17,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 96/3/4*4+2?',
        answer: 18,
        color: 'Red',
        number:18,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 25*3-77-7?',
        answer: 19,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 19,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 1000/10-8*10?',
        answer: 20,
        color: 'RV',
        number: 20,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 121/11*2-1?',
        answer: 21,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 21,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 8*5-40/10-14?',
        answer: 22,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 22,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 45-25/5-17?',
        answer: 23,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 23,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 96/8-12/12+13?',
        answer: 24,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 24,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 25/5+22-2?',
        answer: 25,
        color: 'GV',
        number: 25,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 125/5+5-4?',
        answer: 26,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 26,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 99/3+4-10?',
        answer: 27,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 27,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 75/5+20-7?',
        answer: 28,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 28,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 89-50/10-55?',
        answer: 29,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 29,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 90/10*3+3?',
        answer: 30,
        color: 'RV',
        number: 30,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 69-49*2+60?',
        answer: 31,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 31,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 80/5*2?',
        answer: 32,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 32,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 121/11*2+11?',
        answer: 33,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 33,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 45/15*12-2?',
        answer: 34,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 34,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 52-225+2*4?',
        answer: 35,
        color: 'GV',
        number: 35,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 125/5*2-14?',
        answer: 36,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 36,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 5*12-18-5?',
        answer: 37,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 37,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 4*12/6*5-2?',
        answer: 38,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 38,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 2*25/5*5-11?',
        answer: 39,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 39,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 49/7*7-11+2?',
        answer: 40,
        color: 'RV',
        number: 40,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 5+10*4-4?',
        answer: 41,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 41,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 2*22-49/7+5?',
        answer: 42,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 42,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 3*20-60+43?',
        answer: 43,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 43,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 125/5*2-6?',
        answer: 44,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 44,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 5*4/2*4+5?',
        answer: 45,
        color: 'GV',
        number: 45,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 46/2+45-22?',
        answer: 46,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 46,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 4*36/8*2+11?',
        answer: 47,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 47,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 125/5*2-2?',
        answer: 48,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 48,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 121/11*4+5?',
        answer: 49,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 49,
        size: 'Small'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 80/2+5+5?',
        answer: 50,
        color: 'RV',
        number: 50,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 30*2-10+1?',
        answer: 51,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 51,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 10*5+5-3?',
        answer: 52,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 52,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 9*7-5*2?',
        answer: 53,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 53,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 3*20+4-10?',
        answer: 54,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 54,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 80/2+13+2?',
        answer: 55,
        color: 'GV',
        number: 55,
        size: 'Big'
    },

    {
        question: 'What is 30+20/10+24?',
        answer: 56,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 56,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 6*9+6-3?',
        answer: 57,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 57,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 2*10*2+18?',
        answer: 58,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 58,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 25*2+5+4?',
        answer: 59,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 59,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 16*3+6+6?',
        answer: 60,
        color: 'RV',
        number: 60,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 20*4-20+1?',
        answer: 61,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 61,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 70-6*2+4?',
        answer: 62,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 62,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 5*5*3-12?',
        answer: 63,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 63,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 14*4+20-12?',
        answer: 64,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 64,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 100/2+40-25?',
        answer: 65,
        color: 'GV',
        number: 65,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 100/2+40-24?',
        answer: 66,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 66,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 40+20+2+5?',
        answer: 67,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 67,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 30*2+4+4?',
        answer: 68,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 68,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 70-10+3*3?',
        answer: 69,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 69,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 25*3-15+10?',
        answer: 70,
        color: 'RV',
        number: 70,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 25*3-15+11?',
        answer: 71,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 71,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 80*2-90+2?',
        answer: 72,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 72,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 38*2-2-1?',
        answer: 73,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 73,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 40/2+60-6?',
        answer: 74,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 74,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 15*4+10+5?',
        answer: 75,
        color: 'GV',
        number: 75,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 19*6-14-24?',
        answer: 76,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 76,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 9*8+2+3?',
        answer: 77,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 77,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 4*20/2+38?',
        answer: 78,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 78,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 17*5-10+4?',
        answer: 79,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 79,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 200/4+20+10?',
        answer: 80,
        color: 'RV',
        number: 80,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 12*8+4-19?',
        answer: 81,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 81,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 350/5+30-18?',
        answer: 82,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 82,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 35*3-35+13?',
        answer: 83,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 83,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 10*8+2+2?',
        answer: 84,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 84,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 15*4+35-10?',
        answer: 85,
        color: 'GV',
        number: 85,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 50+20+10+6?',
        answer: 86,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 86,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 50+20+10+7?',
        answer: 87,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 87,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 99-15+2+2?',
        answer: 88,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 88,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 9*9+16-8?',
        answer: 89,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 89,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 10*10-5-5?',
        answer: 90,
        color: 'RV',
        number: 90,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 30*9-200+21?',
        answer: 91,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 91,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 30*9-200+22?',
        answer: 92,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 92,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 13*8/4+67?',
        answer: 93,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 93,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 63+7+8+16?',
        answer: 94,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 94,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 21*5+5-15?',
        answer: 95,
        color: 'GV',
        number: 95,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 55*2/10+85?',
        answer: 96,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 96,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 6*6*3-11?',
        answer: 97,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 97,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 6*6*3-10?',
        answer: 98,
        color: 'Red',
        number: 98,
        size: 'Big'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is 18*4+30-3?',
        answer: 99,
        color: 'Green',
        number: 99,
        size: 'Big'
    },

]